you know if we're both gonna do blaze characters for our next projects we should turn this into a
group cosplay nope not happening a group cosplay must be when people do different characters from
the same series i prefer to cosplay for myself by myself and knock out photo shoots without
interference i have no plans to work with other cosplayers i did notice your photos are pretty
detailed especially for black lily since i intend to go all out and rent out a studio space
holy crap so cool can i come with you i want to see i told you i'm not doing group what if i split
the studio fees with you i've heard some of the swankier places will totally clean you out
oh really want me to pitch in too wait are you saying you want to come she'll need me i help
kitagawa put on her makeup fake eyelashes are hard for her is he serious that's a joke right nope it's
the truth it's pretty goofy though isn't it i'm making fun of you
yeah hmm
yeah
Thank you.
Okay, you can totally ignore all that. No hard feelings. I'm sorry for bothering you with all this. I'm looking forward to your Black Lily photos either way.
I... I could be persuaded. If you wanted to come, just this once, you can.
Hell yes! A cosplay do-out of Juju!
Just this once, though. You heard me say that, right?
This should be fun. But I'd better watch the show first.
Why? What could all that do you? Wouldn't reference photos be enough?
Well, they're a pretty good jumping-off point for sure.
But understanding the source material will help me pick exactly the right fabric for each character.
Oh.
I played Slippery Girls 1 and 2 to make notes on Shizuku-tan.
Yeah!
What?
It was surprisingly moving. The present is naked when the protagonist enters a club room and in her anus.
That's enough. I get it already. You did your research.
Let's see. Flower Princess Blaze already finished airing, right?
Do you know if there's anywhere that I can stream it?
I own the entire series. I can just lend you my box set.
Oh, yeah. That would be great. But are you sure that's okay?
Yeah. It's so much fun. And you can totally binge it. It's only 126 episodes.
A hundred and...
What?
You got a new project, do you?
Yeah. It's an anime thing. But the DVDs are heavy. So I'm gonna go pick it up from Kitagawa tomorrow.
Ah. I'll watch the shop then.
Go have fun.
What's taking him so long? Did I do that bad a job?
It's true I haven't practiced much lately. So I guess...
Hmm...
Wakana?
Hmm? Yes?
Your work has improved.
Huh? Really?
Oh, yes.
Your lines used to be a bit stiff and jagged.
But here, they're looking much softer.
Oh, yeah?
I can't really tell myself.
Hmm.
You know what I think did it? Making that outfit for Maureen.
You even did her makeup, didn't you?
Mm-hmm.
And I'm sure you approached it with the exact same care and concentration you would when painting a Hina doll's face.
See that? To be a great doll maker, you can't only look at dolls, you know.
Look for beauty everywhere. Do that, and I guarantee it'll pay off.
Yes, sir.
Heh heh heh heh heh heh.
Wait, I didn't get here too early, did I? I swear this was the time she gave me.
Sorry, I just woke up.
I started watching Blaze last night, and I just couldn't stop.
Totally my bad.
Why don't we grab my bus point?
20 centimeters.
You could find out.
Uh, Gojo?
You good, bro?
Uh, yeah, I'm sorry.
That's what you're worried about?
We're all good now. Sorry to keep you waiting.
No worries. As long as you're comfortable.
Come on in.
It's not much, but these are for you.
No way! You didn't have to do that.
I wanted to. I've been given these before, so...
Well, thank you.
Oh, dope! Little puddings!
That almost made my heart explode.
Seeing me without makeup is one thing, but without my contacts?
Can't handle it.
Oh, cool! These are from that shop that always has a line! Sweet!
I'm freaking out!
What do I do? I know I'm just picking up research materials, but I've never been to a friend's house before!
Not to mention someone like Kitakawa's house!
No!
I'm so nervous, I'm gonna puke!
I need to get these DVDs from her and get the heck out of here!
Gojo?
Yeah? What can I do for you?
Since you came all this way, we should watch a few episodes.
Ah! Like here? But why?
If we can knock out a couple volumes, you'll have less to carry home!
Uh, I guess?
So let's go, you goof!
Okay. Thanks for inviting me in.
Don't puke, don't puke, don't puke!
Here, this one is my room.
Kitakawa's bedroom!
You can go ahead and sit wherever. Sorry about the mess.
Oh, I'm sure it's...
Yep, this is totally your room.
Huh? Yeah?
Wakuna's anxiety vanished in an instant.
Mom! Dad! Was I that much of a burden to you?
Would you have been better off if I'd never been born?
Nihon!
I...
All I ever wanted was to be loved.
And Soma-kun...
Even Soma-kun didn't want me in the end.
Nihon, no!
Nihon!
If you unleash any more darkness, you'll...
Neon!
Wow.
So when Neon becomes Black Lobelia,
her personality and her appearance change.
It rules, doesn't it?
Wait, Neon?
No, it can't be.
Indeed, Shion.
It has I.
But why, Neon?
Why?
So even Shiontan had no idea that was actually her sister.
I see.
And that's her flower jewel?
Oh, it's pitch black now.
Yeah, because she's off the deep end.
Tragic, right?
Oh, please.
Go away, Mirai.
I told you I don't associate with the other princesses.
Yeah, get lost, loser!
Look how cold she is.
She acts like that with everyone, except for Neon.
She's so cute, it makes me want to die.
Look, Shionchan.
You keep saying that happiness won't last forever.
But you're forgetting something important.
Sadness doesn't last either.
Shut up, shut up, shut up!
Don't talk about things you don't understand!
You're just a cheerful little space cadet.
You don't know how I feel!
Come on!
This is a magical girl show, right?
So why are they just punching each other?
Oh, look!
Here it comes!
The ship!
Oh, are these the boys you mentioned before?
Yeah, that one with the silver hair is Shiontan's crush, Sakuya-kun.
And the one with the black hair is Mirai's older brother, Soma-kun.
Do you see?
Do you see how close they are?
Yeah, you were right.
They are both really handsome.
Look at their uniforms.
They kind of look like our schools, don't they?
Hold up!
Does this count as a home date?
Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, it does!
It totally does!
I mean, we've hung out at home before, but that was different because his grandpa was always around.
But now...
Now...
We're...
Alone together.
I love him!
Holy crap!
I'm having so much fun with him!
A home date with the guy I love is the best!
Like, seriously, the best, the best, the best!
I want this moment to last literally forever!
Not on my watch, bitch!
Oh, I guess you haven't eaten anything but pudding today, huh?
Kill me now!
I can run and grab some takeout.
Want me to go real quick?
Mm-mm.
No, you're good.
I can whip something up.
I'll make enough for both of us.
Oh!
Will you really?
A homemade meal from Kitakawa!
Huh?
A homemade meal from Kitakawa?
Kitakawa?
Why don't I cook?
Huh?
No way!
You cook for me all the time and you're a guest here!
Let me handle this one!
Mm-hmm.
Alright.
Now what should I make?
Oh, whoops.
Forgot a bra.
Ah, it's fine.
Not like he noticed.
Okay.
I have some eggs, some onions, leftover chicken.
Huh.
I could make omelet rice.
Actually.
No.
Holy crap.
Wait, am I really gonna do this?
That's so freaking girly.
Oh my god!
Oh, I'm blushing!
Okay, hurry up and cook, you doofus!
Chop.
God, this sucks!
My eyes are on fire!
Screw you two onions, damn!
What'd I ever do to you?
Hey, this looks pretty good so far.
Oh!
Tasty!
Oh my god, this is like gourmet!
I'm a freaking genius!
Who knew making omelet rice was such a cinch?
Now to wrap this baby up in a little egg blankie and call it good!
Oh.
Thank you for cooking.
Uh-huh.
I, uh...
I'm...
Sorry.
It was looking pretty good till I sort of ruined the omelet.
But I used up all my eggs so I couldn't try again.
So, uh...
No!
You don't have to eat that!
Just...
Did you use anything other than salt and pepper?
Huh?
Oh, yeah.
I cooked it with chicken stock.
And there's some soy sauce in there, too.
I see.
That was a really good idea.
It's delicious.
Huh?
Weirdly, I've never tried that before.
I like it.
Wait.
You're not just being nice?
What?
No, I mean it.
It's very good.
Well, okay.
Thank goodness.
I guess I should eat, too.
Yeah.
Come to mama, you.
I should make this sometime.
It's a nice change from the more traditional Japanese food we usually eat at home.
Kitagawa must really love...
fried rice.
Even if that's true, I'll never give up.
Cause I'm a flower princess!
You can do it.
Me right here.
Need some tissues?
I got you.
Hi, it's Gojo.
I just wanted to check in on the multi-view sketch I sent.
Anything you want me to revise?
No.
It's great.
Thank you.
I'm glad.
But hey, are your sketches always this detailed?
Uh, pretty much.
Oh, that's impressive.
I can go ahead and send funds for the fabric.
How much do you think you'll need?
Oh, I'm not quite sure yet.
Would you be willing to wait until it's complete to pay?
I promise I'll do my best to keep the cost down.
Oh, no problem.
I can do that.
Do you want me to take care of hair and makeup?
Nah, don't worry about it.
I can do that myself.
Sounds like a plan.
But speaking of, I went through all your cosplay photos and I wanted to pick your brain about something.
Uh, sure.
Go ahead.
Thanks.
So I know how to reshape the eyelid.
But for some of these characters, the shape of your eyes looks totally different overall.
How do you pull that off?
Oh.
I use face tape.
Face tape?
Here, let me turn my camera on.
Oh.
Can you see me?
Yeah.
Crystal clear.
I use this.
Cosplay tape can totally change your look if you place it right.
For example, if you want your eyes to look bigger, anchor your tape mid-forehead or above each eye and pull it back over your wig cap.
You'll look more bright-eyed and doll-like.
And you won't have to think about it.
Wow.
Some cosplayers will use tape to sharpen their cheekbones or jawline.
But you get the most bang for your buck like this.
Matching a character's eye shape is always a great detail.
We could have made Shizuku-tan look more droopy-eyed that way.
Thank you.
This is really informative.
You've really never heard of this?
No.
That was my first cosplay experience.
You're kidding, right?
That outfit?
That was your first time making one?
Yeah.
I still have a lot to learn, obviously.
I guess that explains why Kitakawa's photos were taken with a smartphone rather than a real camera.
I don't get you.
You're so...
Okay.
We should maybe plan on taking photos with our camera.
Wait, whose?
Oh, did I not mention this?
My little sister is the one who takes my photos.
Oh, that's cool.
Your sisters are really incredible photographer.
The colors in all of these are amazing.
Well, we do finish them with photo editing software.
That way we can touch up blemishes or even perfect eye color.
Still incredible.
You guys should totally invest in a nice camera, too.
Um, Inui?
What?
If it's not too much trouble, could your sister give me a crash course in cameras?
There's so much I don't know yet.
Probably.
But she is still in middle school, and if we meet all the way out at your place, we wouldn't get home till late.
I would be happy to meet you somewhere.
Okay.
There's a family restaurant near my place if that works for you.
Yes, that's perfectly fine.
Cool.
I'll text you.
Great.
Thanks so much, Inui.
A camera, huh?
There were a lot of fancy-looking ones at the event we went to.
Yes, hello?
I want to come with you!
I'd love to learn how to use a real camera for this stuff.
Uh, sure.
Just let me ask Inui first.
Thanks, bud.
Maureen, if I don't put food in me right now, I'm literally gonna die.
Be right there, Noah.
Go get us a table, okay?
I had no idea Juju had a little sis.
I bet she's way cute.
Like a total clone of Juju, but a little teeny tiny baby version.
Yeah, I can definitely picture that.
I'm so freaking excited now!
It's very nice to meet you.
Hey, don't slouch.
Come on, sit up.
Okay, sorry.
She always gets nervous when she meets new people.
I, uh...
I'm...
I'm Shinju Inui.
And it's a pleasure to make your acquaintance.
Well, she's certainly not what I pictured.
And she's...
She's in middle school?
Oh my god, girl!
Like, I dreamed of being that huge in middle school.
Just how big are you?
Uh...
Kitagawa!
I'm five four and a half on a good day.
I'm, um...
I'm five foot ten?
No way!
Shut up!
I am so jealous!
Of course that's what she meant.
Outro Music
I
Thank you.